A body of work.
Nude is a documentary film directed by Tony Sacco.
NUDE explores perceptions of nudity in art by chronicling the creative process of photographer David Bellemere as
he's commissioned by NU Muses founder Steve Shaw to shoot a fine art calendar of nude photographs.
Self - Art Photographer, played by David Bellemere.
Self, played by Steve Shaw.
Self, played by Rachel Cook.
Self, played by Jessica Clements.
Self, played by Ebonee Davis.
Self, played by Jeannie Park.
Nude is a 2017 American documentary film about a talent search and Pirelli
Calendar-inspired fine art nude calendar production named NU Muses.
The film explores themes of photography, softcore,
creative process, nude photography.